{
    "id": "9a7da5dbd0f64111869bb7f69e2c6fac",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jack, Peter and Mary work at a call center. ………………….. are very industrious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "We",
                "You"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister and I like films. ………………… watch as many films as possible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "We",
                "They",
                "You"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "On my birthday Peter gave ………………… a watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "us",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "On …………………. birthday I gave him a shirt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie sings really well. ……………….. has a golden voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She",
                "He",
                "You"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Albert is in the national football team. …………………. is a good striker.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "He",
                "She",
                "It"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom and Brad are my favorite actors. I like ………………… very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "those"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The elephant has a long trunk. ................................... has also got large ears.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She",
                "He",
                "It"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The spider is an insect. ................................. has eight legs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "It",
                "He",
                "She"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The birds have made several nests on the branches. The nests have baby birds in ...............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}